<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing and Outreach</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/marketing/</guid>
      <description>Strategize and execute campaign across social media channels
  Manage paid content and evaluate outcomes (Facebook Ads)
  Design E-Newsletter (Mailchimp, Constant Contact)
  Design, update, and maintain Wordpress website with html, CSS, Javascript, and Wordpress plugins
  Manage the relationships of interns, volunteers, and scholars through online platform and team events. Successfully grew a network of volunteers over 200% (300+ people) to support additional audience engagement during events</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Production</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/event/</guid>
      <description>Project manage entire event process from initial planning, logistics, and calendaring, to execution on the ground, and post-event reporting
  Coordinated over 300+ public events with up to 50,000 attendance
  Manage pre-event logistics such as timelines, travel and accommodation, vendor agreements, invitations and promotion, staffing, and merch production
  Handle all day-of event execution such as setup, staff training, stage management, and breakdown.
  Type of events: theatrical production, conference, festival, music concert, panel, fundraising gala, screening, award ceremony</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance and Operation Management</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/operation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/operation/</guid>
      <description>  Oversee operating budgets, track expenses, and administer payroll, invoices, and gifts (Excel, Argos, QuickBooks)
  Manage hiring, onboarding, and semi-annual performance evaluation.
  Design staff training materials and activities.
  Experienced in international working/visiting visa regulation, payment, and cultural understanding.
  Oversee the submission of grant proposals, author reports, as well as execute end-of-year solicitation
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Development</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/curation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/curation/</guid>
      <description>  Research and identify potential participating guests, panelists, or artists
  Communicate with curation, audience development, and editorial teams about relevant stories for themes, special projects, and timely events.
  Support the communications team with engaging copy and data to achieve optimal media outcome
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/graphic-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/graphic-design/</guid>
      <description>  Create key art images and logos (Photoshop, Illustrator)
  Design and typeset digital and print publication, including books, playbills, postcards, posters (InDesign)
  Published work including play translations, poetry book, photo book, exhibition catalogue
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>