<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Segal Talks with Taiwanese Theatre Artists  (2020/11)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/tropical-angels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/tropical-angels/</guid>
      <description>Tropical Angels, written by award-winning playwright of HBO&amp;rsquo;s “The Teenage Psychic” Lin Meng-Huan (林孟寰) with music composed by rising New York-based composer Sheng Lei (雷昇), is a musical developed into Chinese and English versions concurrently with the intention to explore different possibilities to devise translated theatre. Directed by David Thomas Cronin. Music-Directed by Sobina Chi Kanter.
From West to East is a discussion to explore how Western-dominated musical theatre has been adapted in the Asian theatre scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEGAL TALKS: Chou Tung-yen, Wu-Kang Chen, &amp; Kathy Hong (2020/4)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/segal-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/segal-talks/</guid>
      <description>Taiwanese theater practitioners, Chou Tung-yen (VERY Theatre), Wu-Kang Chen (HORSE) and Kathy Hong (PANDA), are invited to a Live-streamed conversation with Dir. Frank Hentschker of Martin E. Segal Theatre Center (The Graduate Center, CUNY), to share their thoughts, feelings, and discoveries towards work and life during the pandemic
Learn more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next After Marriage Equality? (2019/11)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/after-marriage-equality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/after-marriage-equality/</guid>
      <description>In May 2019, Taiwan became the first Asian country to legalize same-sex marriage. Taiwanese playwrights, Chao Chi-Yun (趙啟運), Lin Meng-Huan (林孟寰), and Liu Chien-Kuo (劉建幗) have created short plays embracing the achievements and struggles of this historic moment. Directed by Michael Leibenluft of Gung Ho Projects. The readings was followed by a discussion with the playwrights, curators, director, and translator Jeremy Tiang moderated by Linnea Valdivia, Literary Manager for the National Queer Theater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pride Voices: New Plays from Taiwan (2019/11;2018/6)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/pride-voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/pride-voices/</guid>
      <description>Pride Voices featured excerpted readings from The Possible Memoirs of a Traitor by Li-Ying Chien (directed by Knud Adams) and Solo Date by Pao-Chang Tsai (directed and performed by Tsai; dramaturgy by Soriya Chum).Through their plays and stage works Chien and Tsai have reinvigorated the Taiwanese theatre-scape. Blending new media, real-life event, and various performative techniques, their highly political and engaged works give voice to an emerging cultural movement in Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRELUDE Festival (2014-2019)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/prelude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/prelude/</guid>
      <description>The annual PRELUDE festival is dedicated to artists at the forefront of contemporary New York City theatre, dance, interdisciplinary and mediatized performance. PRELUDE offers an array of short performances, readings, and screenings — a completely free survey of the current New York moment and the work being prepared for the next season and beyond—as well as new commissions and panel discussions with artists, scholars, and performers.
Production and Design Team | 2014 - 2018 | Martin E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Festival on Theatre and Performance (2017-2019)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/film-festival/</guid>
      <description>The Segal Center Film Festival on Theatre and Performance is an annual event showcasing films drawn from the world of theatre and performance. The festival presents experimental, emerging, and established theatre artists and filmmakers from around the world to audiences and industry professionals.
Learn more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwanese Waves at SummerStage (2017-2019)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/taiwanese-waves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/taiwanese-waves/</guid>
      <description>Taiwanese Waves produce music waves and bring inspiring talents from Taiwan to the world. The featured event takes place at Central Park as part of City Park Foundation’s Summerstage season, along with other 100 free and benefit performances from 200 artists in Central Park and 17 neighborhood parks across New York City.
Volunteer Coordinator | 2017 - 2019 | SummerStage at Central Park (New York)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PEN World Voices:International Play Festival (2014-2019)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/pen/</guid>
      <description>As part of the PEN World Voices Festival of International Literature, World Voices: International Play Festival showcases play readings by ten of the world’s most respected dramatists. With writers hailing from four different continents, the International Play Festival generates a conversation on art, politics, dreams, war, and philosophy, meant to give American audiences a rich awareness of global dialogues. Readings will be followed by a discussion with the playwright.
Learn more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Chinese at Samuel French OOB Festival(2018/9)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/bad-chinese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/bad-chinese/</guid>
      <description>Bad Chinese is comedy about Asian/Asian-American identity and the yearning for a sense of cultural authenticity. Written by Ruth Tang. Directed by Peter J. Kuo.
The Off Off Broadway Short Play Festival (OOB) is the nation’s leading short play festival. Beyond playwrights, the Festival has given voice to many emerging directors, performers, and production companies.bal dialogues. Readings will be followed by a discussion with the playwright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Broken Record at NYC Fringe Festival(2015/8)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/broken-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/broken-record/</guid>
      <description>The Broken Record written by Jonathan Louis Dent and directed by Megan Sandberg-Zakian, examines the violence between black youth and police officers in the United States, exposing the fury, helplessness, and grief we feel watching these stories play on repeat, and asking: how can these fatal encounters finally be stopped?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gutting (2015/9)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/gutting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/gutting/</guid>
      <description>Gutting, written by Jeremy J. Kamps and directed by Zoey Martinson, follows fourteen-year-old Kali returning home to post-Katrina Lower 9th Ward. Commemorating the 10th anniversary of the hurricane, this production of GUTTING accompanied by community programming addressing the related issues of displacement, gentrification and racism.
Presented by Company Cypher, Amy Rafa, and Sarah Stites.
Read more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Train/Stopped Clock/Untitled Waiting (2013/8)</title>
      <link>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/upcoming-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chacajliu.github.io/projects/upcoming-train/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Dream Up Festival, Theater for the New City. Written &amp;amp; Directed by Dennis Yueh-Yeh Li
Theatre After Pozzo (TAP) named after Pozzo, the antagonist in Samuel Beckett’s master piece Waiting For Godot. Formed by a group of non-traditional young theatre artists with various theatre-related backgrounds, TAP aims to create inspiring, thought-provoking original productions beyond entertainment, addressing controversial social issues as well as the complexity and ambiguity of human nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
